=Born Again=
=Episode 5=
Ye Shen.
Do you think
it will end today?
Will dawn break?
I don't know either.
Wait, Ye Shen.
You haven't told me
how you entered the loop.
Did you also die?
You were also reborn?
I've never died.
Then how come you...
A doctor?
No wonder you have
all those strange books at home.
I work at a private hospital,
providing exclusive medical services
for the elite families in this city.
So,
every time you got hurt,
you were brought to me.
I was the one who gave you
the final rescue.
(The first time,)
(the champagne tower's glass
nearly shredded you.)
(There were 147 stitches.)
(I gave you 147 stitches in total.)
(The second time,)
(the allergy nearly
destroyed your skin.)
(You loved to look your best,)
(but ended up with such a fate.)
All of this happened
because of my choice.
How could it be your fault?
Every loop
and every death
was caused by those people.
(From the very first loop,)
(I watched you die in front of me
every single time.)
(I tried everything to bring you back,)
(but I could never change your fate.)
Dr. Ye,
stop saving her.
The patient is beyond saving.
So,
since fate has given us this chance,
we can definitely change the outcome.
Ye Shen,
have you ever thought
about what if this loop
never ends?
Then I'll stay with you
until you find true freedom.
Watch out!
Ye Shen?
Ye Shen!
Gu Xiaotang!
You wretch!
You humiliated me in front of everyone!
Now the Lu family has cast me aside!
(If I just run away now,)
(even if the loop ends,)
(Ye Shen will never come back.)
I'll kill you!
Lu Qingyuan,
see
you
next time.
Ye Shen.
Ye Shen!
Why am I at home?
What's going on?
Today isn't the wedding day.
The loop
is a full week earlier.
(One week before the wedding)
Baby.
(Lu Qingyuan.)
I brought you roses.
What's wrong, Xiaotang?
Are you feeling unwell?
Don't touch me!
Xiaotang?
What's wrong? It's me.
We're getting married in a week, honey.
(No, I can't let him get suspicious.)
(It's a week before everything happens.)
(I don't know where Ye Shen is yet.)
(I'm completely alone now.)
(I can't provoke him.)
I-I'm a bit hypoglycemic.
I feel dizzy.
You scared me.
Then get up.
I'll warm some milk for you, okay?
No need. I have to go.
Xiaotang, I'm here.
Look what I brought you.
Those super delicious croissants.
Are you going out so early?
What's her problem again?
I find it strange as well.
Why did the loop start earlier?
Was it because of Ye Shen's death
or my choice?
Could
the loop's rules have changed?
I'm back to seven days ago.
So it means nothing has happened.
It also means
everything could happen again.
No,
I must find Ye Shen immediately.
(Outpatient Clinic)
Dr. Ye.
Ye Shen!
♪Time falls like dust upon you♪
♪You don't have to walk the path alone♪
♪In the instant the wind rises♪
♪Dust illuminates you like stars♪
♪You don't have to count every flicker♪
♪Following the tracks
of the days that were♪
I thought I'd never see you again.
It's so good to see you again.
Why did the loop start earlier?
Xiaotang?
What are you doing here?
Don't you remember the loop?
The loop?
What loop?
(Oh no, he doesn't remember.)
(Am I the only one who came back?)
Gu Xiaotang,
you actually still remember me?
Of course I remember.
We were high school classmates.
We...
We've been through so much together.
Xiaotang.
Running out in such a panic,
you came here to meet your classmate.
Lu Qingyuan, you followed me?
How could that be?
I was worried about you.
You ran out
when having a hypoglycemic episode.
And
Xiaotang's classmate...
Ye Shen?
You're a doctor.
It's a tough profession, isn't it?
Earning so little money each month.
Too tough.
You were Xiaotang's classmate.
Why not come work for me?
Xiaotang is always good to her friends.
I know her very well.
You don't know her.
Can't you see she's unhappy right now?
She's my wife.
Of course I know her.
Not yet.
What do you mean?
What are you trying to say?
(No,)
(Ye Shen doesn't remember the loop now.)
(I shouldn't drag him into this mess.)
(He's already died for me once.)
Lu Qingyuan,
the wedding prep isn't done yet.
Let's go back first.
Alright.
By the way,
Mr. Ye,
since you were Xiaotang's classmate,
you should also come to our wedding.
No need for a gift.
♪The face deep in the heart♪
♪Suddenly clear and hazy♪
♪Across time and space, eyes meet again♪
♪Deeply trapped in the vortex♪
♪Searching for familiar outlines♪
♪Persistently guarding,
endlessly cycling♪
♪Even for just a second♪
♪If raindrops flow backward
into the sky♪
♪And sunlight reverses♪
♪As the sun rises and sets,
we reunite with yesterday♪
♪I'll build a dream with you♪
♪Upon the ruins, spring breeze arrives♪
♪Even if there's no end,
I won't regret the start♪
♪Eternity like a day, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to recognize my eyes♪
♪Following the tracks
of the days that were♪
♪A day like a lifetime, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to remember my name♪
♪I'll be the dawn you haven't seen♪